Guide to the Firebrand Books records, 1984-2000.
Firebrand Books records,
- Series III. Financial Records
  - Vendor Files: Photography and Manuscript Services, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Vendor Files: Office Supplies, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Vendor Files: UPS, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Vendor Files: Shipping, Maintenance, Legal, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Series IV. Conferences and Related Activities
  - 6th International Book Fair, Australia, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 5th International Book Fair, Amsterdam, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - 4th International Book Fair, Barcelona, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 3rd International Book Fair, Montreal, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 2nd International Book Fair, Oslo, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Lambda Literary Awards, 1995-1999 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Lambda Literary Awards, 1989-1994 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - ALA (American Library Association), 1991 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - ALA, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - ALA, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - ALA, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - ALA, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - OutWrite, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - OutWrite, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - OutWrite, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - OutWrite, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - OutWrite, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - OutWrite, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - OutWrite, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - OutWrite, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - OutWrite, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - ABA (American Bookseller's Association), 1997 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - ABA, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - ABA, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - ABA, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - ABA, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - ABA, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - ABA, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - ABA, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - ABA, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - ABA, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - ABA, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - ABA, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - ABA, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Miami Book Fair, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - 1st Nicaraguan Book Fair, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - 13th National Women's Music Festival, Bloomington, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - San Francisco Book Fair, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Misc. Conferences and Book Fairs Attended, 1986-1999 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Behind Our Masks, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Celebrating Joan, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Feminist Writers Workshops, 1986-1993 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Great Midwestern Bookshow, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - "I Am Your Sister" Conference, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 44)
  - Iowa Conference Against Racism, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 45)
  - Jerusalem Book Fair, 1988-1992 (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - Women and the Law Conference-Cancelled, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - Women and the Law Conference, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - 1985 Women in Print Conference, 1984-1986 (Box 64, Folder 49)
  - 1995 Women in Print Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 50)
  - Human Sexuality Collection Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Human Sexuality Collection Correspondence, 1990-1998 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Series V. Administrative Information and Posters
  - Firebrand Employees and Interns, 1987-2000 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Mailing List: Organizations, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising, 1997-2000 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - 13 Posters from Firebrand Office Walls (Mapcase-folder 1)